# JAMES PARK FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER





0210-491-495

https://github.com/jpjh1001

# **ABOUT ME**

I am ready to utilise my expertise in software development to connect with the world.

I am much intrigued by the everevolving technology and to keep up with its rapid pace, I strive to be consistent in the state of learning. And now I am excited to take part in this industry.

My experiences in other fields have broadened my approach to problemsolving and I appreciate the problemsolving aspect of programming and working in teams to achieve a united goal.

When I am not online, I like going to the gym, meeting new people, watching sports, and learning new languages.

# RELEVANT SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS
- Javascript, TypeScript
- React, Redux
- Node.js
- SQlite3 with knex
- Express.js

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Apprentice Software developer at DevAcademy Aotearoa, Auckland

Jan 2023 - May 2023

In an intense 17-week software development bootcamp, I gained the knowledge of becoming a full-stack web developer. Not only did I learn technical skills such as Javascript, Typescript, React, and Redux, but the course also enhanced my human skills to better understand myself and others. As a final group project, I was involved in a self-improvement app (an online scheduler) and I took the role of a frontend developer. While working on the project, it reminded me of how meticulous I had to be to prevent the app from lacking coordination among numerous features to collectively bring the app as a whole.

## Career Gap

Feb 2015 - Jan 2023

## • English teacher, (South Korea)

Nov 2014 - Feb 2015

- I displayed my skills as a leader/teacher, organising how each day should be implemented
- I demonstrated my communication skills to the students, helping students to improve their pronunciation and conversation skills.
- Supermarket team member, Homeplus (South Korea)

Nov 2011 - Feb 2013

- I displayed customer service skills to promote products of certain brands
- As part of the sales team, I demonstrated good communication and teamwork among my coworkers which lead to good synergy.
- I delivered my attentive skills through regular checks of which shelves needed restocking/reorganising.

#### **EDUCATION HISTORY**



# **Dev-Academy Aotearoa Software development**

Year of Graduation: 2023



# **Graduate Diploma in Economics**

Institution: The University of Queensland

Attended: 2016



# Bachelor of Commerce majoring in Accounting and Finance

Institution: The University of Melbourne

Year of Graduation: 2015

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**



# **Software Development Level 6**

Institution: Dev-Academy Aotearoa 2023



**UCAT** ·University Clinical Aptitude test for Australia and New Zealand (UCAT ANZ) 90 percentile (2020)